So in this section, we'll have a look at boot animation.
So you might have already seen this boot animation.
It's basically the splash screen when you start the emulator or when you start to a mobile device.
So we'll see how we can change that in this section.
Changing the boot animation is quite straightforward and it's not that complicated.
So if you have a look at areas B, I am opening one sample boot animation file.
So if you go onto the car product boot animations, so this is the one or the automotive build against
automotive build the boot animation is under this particular car product boot animation.
So under the boot animation there is a zip file which contains different folders and within that it
has got this animation.
So this is the animation which you would have noticed while loading the emulator.
You see it has got a set of Benji files.
It is actually displayed sequentially to show this animation.
So the boot animation is simply a zip file with all the PND files and it has also got a description
text which we have deployed.
So it has some information.
I will explain to you later what exactly these.
So in summary, mood animation is just a zip file with a set of BND files.
So this is the default one.
So here if you go, you can see this is a small animation.
So this is how the animation is working there.
And finally there is an Android display, right?
This is the one where you see the android.
These are the patterns.
So they I do not have seven being defined to show this and they're stuck.
So changing the boot animation will trigger the following steps.
So first you need to create a folder structure with the sequence file.
So this is a folder and it has got part zero, part one and how many parts you have and then you how
you should have their description or text.
So you have the folder called Boot Animation A32 and it contains all these part folders.
And if within the part folders it has got to be in defines and then under that you have the description
text.
Okay, so this is the folder structure.
So if you want to create your own boot animation, you have to foster creative folder.
And inside the folder you should have the part folders like part zero one, two, three, four, five.
Okay.
And based on the number of pages you have, based on how big is your animation, then you should have
one description or text.
The assistant packs teach you some information rules.
Have a look at that and then our next slide.
Okay.
So, so this is the content of DSC.
So DSC duty actually contains this is an example content of the file.
So in this case, I have three folders, part 012 and the first line, first line is actually the solution.
So this is the horizontal resolution that is a with 832 and 520, the vertical resolution.
And then you have got the frame rate, which is actually 30.
And in the second line, the first digit starts with C and then you have got the number of looked.
So this explains how many times it has to be loop.
Think how many times this files has to be displayed and then this is the seconds post time in seconds.
So this is the post time, 30 seconds.
Okay.
And then you have go for the name, which is part serial.
And then here we have again the next line which has got one loop, zero post second and then part one.
And then this is the third line serial c00 part two.
So if you have three folders, then you will have fine lines over here and it will be like part zero
one, two, three.
So it's quite straightforward and simple.
And once you have prepared this file, just compress the folder and then keep it in any of the path
within is B and then you have to edit the route and keep.
So the Condor M came in the sights in the same folder here under the car you can see the cartoon name
over here we have the line which actually copies boot animation to system image.
You have to edit that and just add this and then build and wait for me to complete.
And then and then the animation stuff is ready.
So in the next section, so we'll go ahead and implement our on board animation.
So this is a practical section where we are going to implement a boot animation.
So let's play this one.
Exactly.
I'm going to do so.
I am planning to change my bootloader as a famous domino theory in intro.
I hope you have seen this for sure.
So this is what exactly I am planning to make.
Okay, so this line for this MGM angel, that's what I'm going to show.
Okay, so what I have done is I have taken this video and split it into different, different sprint
frames.
Okay.
So I have this here now.
So I have split the video into different, different DNG files, basically.
So you can do this online if you want.
Like you can just search for split to you split video into frames.
Then you get some online online links as well.
So you can either do it online or download some software to do that.
So check it out.
So that's quite easy.
So I have done that already and I have kept it in this folder.
So I hope you remember in previous theory sections, I explain to you what exactly is the folder structure
of the boot animations.
So this is my boot animation boot folder.
And inside that you have the part, serial part, one part to that party.
So mine is a small intro.
So I have just taken only the lion part or the cartoon afterwards.
So it's only 59 being device.
While if you check the original one from Google, that has got a lot of being G.
So if you want, you can make a big one.
So for this example, I had taken a very small one.
Okay.
So once this is done and once you have created the folder structure, you have to edit this description,
etc...
So here you need to give the resolution of your image.
And that is Mike 86, 44, 80, and the frame rate is 30.
Okay.
And it has got four folders basically is part zero, which has just a blank file.
So let's use here as well, maybe be and it is against okay, here you have the three folders where
we have the attack.
So let's save this.
Okay?
Save it.
And now we need to actually skip this content and create a creative zip file, basically.
Okay.
For skipping it, you should use this document that if you don't use a storm method, it may not work,
actually.
Because in my case, I was initially trying to just right click and compress.
So this will not work.
Why do you need to do is basically just open this up in the command prompt.
So I am already in this folder, Martin, in this folder.
So what I need to do is I need to slip it and give a store method, basically.
So this is the storm right there.
And then give them the zip file name, then give all the contents of the flap.
So this is the command, which basically you need to do.
So the most important part is that you need to use the store method.
The storm method in this case is store and this is the zip command.
So in case if you don't have zip, just go ahead and install zip.
You know, just zip it like this.
Okay.
So I'm just going to zip it.
So it's done.
The shipping is done.
So now I have got the boot up.
Super.
Just turn it and put it over here.
So this is the one.
So I have the following here.
So now come back to the initiative code where we have the boot animation, and here you need to rename.
In my case, I did it already, so that's why it's moved to C.
Otherwise it would be boot animation 832 which is the default one will be coming here.
Just rename it to boot or slip in the product copy files and then save it and then come back to the
areas, be up.
So and then just go ahead and build it.
Yeah.
So you don't need to find that the code or empty is modifying and it's regenerating.
So it may take maybe 2 minutes or something to build because I have already built it.
So let's wait for some time.
Meanwhile.
And so the most important thing you need to keep in mind is this part of constructing the folder structure
is make sure you have named all the folders correctly and then in the description, just make sure you
have given the for the names correctly, which both should match correctly.
Otherwise you will get into unnecessary delays in implementation.
Okay.
Because I had only one issue when I tried implementing these, I had got only one issue and that was
due to this C stored method.
Okay.
So if you use a proper stored method, then you know and follow these steps, then it is quite simple
and straightforward.
Okay, so let's see whether this is already done.
Now it's 98% age, so maybe in a couple of minutes should be done.
Yeah.
So it's done.
So I took 2 minutes in my case.
So depending upon your PC, it may take longer or shorter.
Okay, so let me immolate this.
So I have just used no snap snapshot load so that we can see the loading.
I'm doing a callable basically here because if you run an emulator once and you try running it, it
will just boot from the snapshot.
So it's better to always cold boot in this case because you want to see the bootloader, so just run
it.
So it is called boot requested by the user.
Let's wait.
Okay, so we have it here.
So this is our bootloader.